vessoft.com 2019-04-19

# Privacy Policy – Vessoft

Welcome to the Vessoft Privacy Policy!

Your privacy is very important for us. That’s why this privacy policy stipulates the terms of how we collect, process and use your personal information.

#### What is personal information?

This privacy policy uses the term “personal information” the meaning of which is defined by the law. Generally speaking, it means any information that can be used to uncover your identity.

#### Collecting personal information

Vessoft collects personal information in order to improve our service. We may collect and store different types of personal information:

  * information about your computer and about the visiting and use of this website, including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of a website visit;
  * information that you provide to us when using the services on our website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services;
  * information containing in the messages or concerning any message which you send to or through our website;
  * any other personal information that you choose to send us.

#### Using personal information

We use all the collected information to provide, maintain, protect and improve existing services as well as to develop new services, and protect our users.

Collected personal data of a client is used for/to:

  * administration of the website and internal operation;
  * personalise our website for you;
  * consideration of requests and complaints concerning our website that were made by you or about you.

#### Disclosing personal information

Vessoft guarantees that it will not transfer, sell, lease or otherwise give out your personal information to third parties except for these reasons:

  * if the law requires it;
  * in connection with any current or possible court or executive orders, warrants or decrees;
  * in case the user fails to implement the relevant Vessoft terms and conditions including the detection of potential violations;
  * if the rights, property, privacy or security of Vessoft, our staff or users are in danger;
  * in the case of fraud, security violation or technical issues.

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or people for the processing according to our instructions and current privacy policy as well as adherence of other appropriate criteria of the privacy and security.

Vessoft may share non-personal information, which does not identify the user in any way, with other users and partners, including publishers, advertisers or owners of the associated sites.

#### Security of personal information

Our website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. We do not make any statements or provide a guarantee concerning the privacy practices of any third party website and we are not responsible for the privacy policy or content of any third party website.

We and third parties use cookies, web beacons, mobile ad identifiers, and other similar technologies to collect the anonymous traffic data, according to our own privacy policy, which are important to simplify the navigation and administration of the site as well as to improve overall quality of our services. Please check the “Help” menu in your internet browser for information regarding how to manage your cookie preferences.

Our privacy policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise Vessoft or our services and may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to place and provide relevant ads.

Vessoft uses the Disqus service which allows the users to discuss and comment the site content. The Vessoft moderators have a right to edit or delete the users comments, if they think it's necessary, and also can delete the user's comments by his/her demande. The information provided by Disqus during the authorization, is subject to the Disqus privacy policy. We do not bear the responsibility for the information provided by the Disqus service.

#### Protection of the children personal information

We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent, unless it is permitted by law in the respective countries (e.g. for children up to 13 years in the USA or children up to 16 years in most European countries). If we find out that a child under this age has provided us with personal information, we will delete it in accordance with applicable law.

#### Change of terms

Our privacy policy may be changed from time to time. Any privacy policy changes will be posted on this page.

#### Language

The languages of the current privacy policy are [Ukrainian](https://uk.vessoft.com/software/info/privacy-policy) and **English**. In case of conflict of Ukrainian or English with any other translation of this agreement, Ukrainian and English shall prevail.

#### Other

The section titles are indicated just for the convenience and do not affect the interpretation of this document.

Thank you for visiting our website.
